A Guide to the Pocahontas Mines Collection, 1883-1997
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II. Unscanned rolls, 1883-1997, 360 Cubic Feet; 463 boxes
  - Peerless Coal & Coke Company (Box 686)
    - [Technical Drawings] Peerless Coal & Coke Co., Technical drawings of surface facilities of Peerless Mine (30 Sheets), 1956-1960 (Box 686)
  - Bottom Creek, Lick Branch, Delta Technical Drawings (Box 686)
    - [Technical Drawings] Bottom Creek Mine Technical Drawings (Box 686)
    - [Technical Drawings] Lick Branch Mine Surface and Technical Drawings (Box 686)
    - [Technical Drawings] Delta Mine Surface Drawings. (Box 686)
  - OSM #700764, No. 3 Mine Map - Section No. 1, 2, 4 (Box 687)
  - OSM #700752, Angle Mine, No. 3 seam (Box 687)
  - OSM #700783, Map #2 Boissevain 6-1. Shawnee no. 3 seam (Box 687)
  - OSM #700469 (Box 687)
  - OSM #700819 Berwin, No. 1, 2, 3 drits, 58 (Box 688)
  - OSM #700803, T-left, Smith Tract Lands, No. 5 mains, No. 89 (Box 688)
  - OSM #700827, Itmann #1, #2 (Box 688)
  - 48. OSM #700814, Lynchburg, No. 9 Seam (Box 688)
  - OSM #700845, 62 Berwin, No. 5 Seam [also says Berwin No. 4 Seam, No. 5 Mine], 1955-1961 (Box 689)
  - OSM #700842, Piedmont Sheet #1, ca. 1950s (Box 689)
  - OSM #700800, JenkinJones South Fork No. 4 Seam, ca. 1960s (Box 689)
  - 72. OSM #700847, Warrior Coal Co., Warrior Coal Co., War, West Virginia (Box 689)
  - Two maps of Crane Creek Mines, No. 3 Seam: OSM #700834, Crane Creek No. 2; Map of Crane Creek Coal and Coke Company, Crane Creek No. 1, McComas, Mercer County, West Virginia, 1906/06 (Box 690)
  - OSM #700853, Ragland Slope (Box 690)
  - OSM #700840, Gooney Otter (covel), Arista (Box 690)
  - Unidentified section of a room and pillar coal mine. (Box 690)
  - OSM #700150, Delta, 127. (Box 691)
  - Ansted No. 2 Mine, Page Upper Seam, 14 Left to 24 Left and 25 Left to 33 Left (Inclusive) (Box 691)
  - 107. OSM #700755, Jenkin Jones Mine located on North Fork of Tug River, map no. 5. G-4 (Box 691)
  - 7. OSM #700758, Jenkin Jones No. 5 mains (Box 691)
  - 130. OSM #700152, Norfolk No. 3 Seam, McDowell County and Mercer County, West Virginia (Box 692)
  - OSM #700767, No. 4 Mine Sheet 1, Itmann No. 4 Seam (Box 692)
  - Pig Creek District, No. 2 Mine, No. 6 Mine, No. 6 East Mine, No. 11 Mine, No. 4 Seam, United States Map No. 4 (Box 692)
  - OSM #700838, Modoc, Active (Box 693)
  - OSM #700829, Big Stick, 10Rt-Active (Box 693)
  - OSM #700760, Itmann No. 1 Mine (Box 693)
  - [Technical Drawings] Deerfield & Itmann Tipple upgrade drawings, 1950-1960 (Box 694)
  - Assorted technical and architectural drawings produced by the Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Pocahontas, Virginia, Engineering Office (60 sheets), ca. 1940s- 1950s (Box 694)
    Includes several floor plans for local churches and company stores.
  - Miscellaneous maps, drawings, and charts relating to Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. projects and properties (50 sheets), ca. 1940s-1950s (Box 694)
    Has a chart detailing the operating mines of Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. and data about each mine. Including coal sample analysis.
  - [Technical Drawings] additions and upgrades to Jenkin Jones Tipple (94 sheets), ca. 1940s-1950s (Box 694)
  - 5 Room and Pillar maps (Box B23)
  - Unidentified Mine Map of New 35 and No. 5 Mains, Pocahontas Coal Co., undated (Box B57)
  - Maps of mains, panels, mines, including 3-C, Extractors, Pinnacle, Cabin Creek, G and A Coal Co., Guyan, Farley, Sugar Run, Sioux Coal Company, etc., 1978-1982 (Box B59)
  - The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company location maps and production charts, 1969 (Box B62)
  - Assorted property, railroad, and other maps and charts, ca. 1960s-1980s (Box B62)
- Series III. Books, 1914-1995, 64.48 Cubic Feet; 62 boxes (2940 vols.)
  Series III. Books, 1914-1995, contains 2940 vols. in 62 boxes, totaling 64.48 cu. ft. It consists of mainly field notebooks from mine surveys and some related papers for surveys. There are publications in boxes B61 and B62.
  - No. 1 Mine, vols. 437-455, 1965-1966 (Box B01)
    (19 ledgers)
  - No. 1 Mine, vols. 441-445, 1963-1968 (Box B01)
    (5 ledgers)
  - Deerfield, 436-437 (Box B01)
    (2 ledgers)
  - Itmann (1/4 survey), 601-608, 1949-1952 (Box B01)
    (8 ledgers)
  - Buckeye Mine (surveys), 1967-1974 (Box B02)
    (19 vols.)
  - Eckman Mine (surveys), 1968-1970 (Box B02)
    (17 vols.)
  - Eckman-Page (surveys), 1970-1982 (Box B02)
  - Killarney, 1961 (Box B02)
    (1 ledgers)
  - Crane Creek, 1974-1976 (Box B02)
  - Arista, 1961-1962 (Box B02)
  - Pageton, 1974-1975 (Box B02)
  - Itmann, vols. 609-620, 1952-1953 (Box B03)
    (12 ledgers)
  - Itmann (1/4 survey), 601-620, 1949-1953 (Box B03)
    (20 ledgers)
  - Itmann (surveys, cross-sections), 1946-1949, 1958-1959, 1963, 1968, 1971 (Box B03)
    (16 vols.)
  - Sewell Seam (Box B03)
  - Upper Pinn Creek (Box B03)
  - Guyandotte Mine (surveys), 1958-1962 (Box B04)
    (12 vols.)
  - Itmann Mine (surveys), 1953, undated (Box B04)
    (4 vols.)
  - Extractors, Inc., 1975-1982 (Box B04)
    (3 vols.)
  - G and A Coal Co., 1958-1959 (Box B04)
    (8 vols.)
  - G.S.C., 1958-1959 (Box B04)
  - Deerfield Belt, 1976 (Box B04)
    (1 vol.)
  - S. and C. No. 8, 1980-1986 (Box B04)
  - No. 3 Mine, 1960-1986 (Box B04)
  - Willie-Scrap, 1978 (Box B04)
  - Buckeye, vol. 25, 1978 (Box B04)
  - Rock Heading, 1981-1982 (Box B04)
  - Untitled, 1978-1982 (Box B04)
  - Long Branch Tipple, 1948-1949 (Box B05)
  - Itmann, 1947-1949 (Box B05)
    (7 vols.)
  - Itmann Lots, nos. 3-6, 1955-1958 (Box B05)
    (4 ledgers)
  - Sewell Seam Strip, vol. 2, 1972 (Box B05)
  - Rich Creek Strip, 1969 (Box B05)
  - L. Spring Strip, 1970 (Box B05)
  - Kepler, 1967 (Box B05)
  - Itmann, 1947-1983 (Box B05)
    (35 vols.)
  - Loose paper, Pinnacle Creek, Itmann, and assorted mines, undated (Box B05)
  - No. 1 Mine, 1925-1930 (Box B06)
    (5 vols.)
  - Killarney Mine, 1939-1957 (Box B06)
  - No. 3 Mine, 1962 (Box B07)
  - Itmann, 1950-1977 (Box B07)
    (24 vols.)
  - Deerfield, 1955-1966 (Box B07)
  - Modoc Mine, Vol. A 15, 1974 (Box B07)
  - No. 4 Mine, 1967-1973 (Box B07)
    (15 vols.)
  - Sugar Run, Vols. 2-3, 1963-1965 (Box B07)
  - Cabin Creek, Vol. 1, 1960 (Box B07)
  - Still Run Strip, 1965-1966 (Box B07)
  - Reflex, Photographic Record, Crozer Coal & Land Co., 1981 (Box B07)
  - Assorted survey books / field notebooks (Box B07)
    (9 vols.)
  - Killarney Mine, 1928-1951 (Box B08)
    (10 vols.)
  - No. 1 Mine, 1927-1932 (Box B08)
  - Unidentified, 1934-1944 (Box B08)
  - Loup Creek Colliery Books, 1944 (Box B08)
    (2 vols.)
  - Lynco, 1972-1976 (Box B08)
  - Page, 1926-1959 (Box B08)
  - Eckmann-Page, 1969-1976 (Box B08)
  - No. 4 Seam (levels), vols. 1-11, 1967-1973 (Box B09)
    (11 ledgers)
  - No. 4 Seam (CL and 1/4 survey), vols. 1-12, 1966-1973 (Box B09)
  - No. 4 Seam (CL), vols. 1, 4-9, 11-12, 1966-1973 (Box B09)
    (9 ledgers)
  - Itmann (1/4 survey), vols. 621-635, 1953-1955 (Box B09)
    (15 ledgers)
  - Itmann, 1956-1973 (Box B10)
    (18 vols.)
  - Deerfield, 1953-1956 (Box B10)
  - 6-1 Check Survey, 1973-1976 (Box B10)
  - Bishop, 1963-1981 (Box B10)
  - Reed Strip, 1976-1977 (Box B10)
  - Coal Stockpiles, 1983-1984 (Box B10)
    (6 vols.)
  - L296 #1-2, L297 #1-2, L298 #1-2, L299 #1-2, L300-L309 (Box B10)
  - Contract Mines, including Sun Shine, 1978-1979 (Box B10)
  - Itmann (1/4 survey), vols. 636-640, 1955-1956 (Box B11)
  - Deerfield (1/4 survey), vols. 621-640, 1953 (Box B11)
  - Itmann (CL), vols. 396-415, 1954-1956 (Box B11)
  - Unidentified (CL), vols. 396-403, 1954-1955 (Box B11)
  - No. 1 Mine (CL and 1/4 survey), no. 456-472, 1969-1975 (Box B12)
    (17 ledgers)
  - No. 1 Mine (survey), vol. 1, 1977 (Box B12)
  - No. 1 Mine (CL) vols. 469-475, 1974-1980 (Box B12)
    (7 ledgers)
  - Unidentified, 1981, 1991 (Box B12)
  - Vol. 9029, 1954 (Box B12)
  - Vol. 9012, undated (Box B12)
  - Boissevain Strip, vol.1, 1975 (Box B12)
  - Amonate No. 1, 1980 (Box B12)
  - Whitaker, 1977-1978 (Box B12)
  - Lillybrook Killarney Mine, vol. 1, 1961 (Box B12)
  - Unidentified (CL), vols. 403-415, 1953-1956 (Box B13)
    (13 ledgers)
  - Deerfield (1/4 survey), vols, 661-667, 669, 1960 (Box B13)
  - Itmann (1/4 survey), vols. 661-668, 670, 1959-1960 (Box B13)
  - Deerfield (CL), vols. 11-20, 1956-1959 (Box B13)
    (10 ledgers)
  - Deerfield (1/4 survey), vols. 1-12, 1956-1960 (Box B13)
  - GSC (CL), vol. 2, 1959 (Box B14)
  - Cranebrake, vol. 1, 1977 (Box B14)
  - Coalbank, vol. 830, 1975 (Box B14)
  - F-Shaft VP (?), L-295, 1981, 1988 (Box B14)
  - Maitland Shaft (?), Vol. 1, 1967 (Box B14)
  - Contract Mines, vols. 3, 5, 1979-1981 (Box B14)
  - Bishop Stripping, vol. 3000, 1972-1973 (Box B14)
  - Low Gap Horsepen Strip, vol. 1204, 1975-1976 (Box B14)
  - Coal Bank No. 9 Seam, 1976 (Box B14)
  - Keowee, vol. 1, 1977 (Box B14)
  - Reed Strip and Boissevain, 1975-1976 (Box B14)
  - Horsepen Stripping, vols. 1200-1201, 1203, 1972-1975 (Box B14)
    (3 ledgers)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Boundary Line, 9036 (Box B14)
  - Shawnee Mountain and Eckman No. 13 Seam, vols. 2-5, 1978-1981 (Box B14)
  - Faraday Land, 9012-9013 (Box B14)
  - Warrior Coal Co. (traverse book), nos. 1-2, 1925-1926 (Box B14)
  - Itmann (check survey), vols. 401-403, 1949-1954 (Box B14)
  - Deerfield (levels), vols. 2-6, 1956-1958 (Box B14)
  - Itmann Centers, no. 351 (Box B14)
  - Itmann No. 11 Seam, vol. 300, 1961-1962 (Box B14)
  - Deerfield (levels), vols. 1-3, 5-7, 1954-1960 (Box B14)
    (6 ledgers)
  - Deerfield, 1949-1950 (Box B14)
  - Deerfield, vols. 2-3, 5-6, 1948-1952 (Box B14)
  - Comker Coal Co. levels, undated (Box B14)
  - Big Bridge, Amonate, Vol. 106, undated (Box B14)
  - Deerfield (CL), vols. 11-21, 1956-1960 (Box B15)
  - Deerfield side of Itmann (CL), vols. 416-435, 1956-1959 (Box B15)
  - Itmann (CL), 416-436, 1956-1959 (Box B15)
  - Check Survey, vols. 401-402, 404, 1949-1957 (Box B16)
  - Unidentified (CL), vol. 389, 1954 (Box B16)
  - Deerfield (check survey), 1956 (Box B16)
  - Itmann 3 Mine (CL), vols. 65, 73-80, 85-87, 89-91, 93-94, 96, 1975-1986 (Box B16)
  - Itmann 3 Mine (levels), vols. 3-8, 10, 11, 1966-1975 (Box B16)
  - Cabin Creek, vols. 1-6, 1961 (Box B16)
  - Cabin Creek (cut site), 1960 (Box B16)
  - Cabin Creek (levels), vol. 2, 1961-1962 (Box B16)
  - Itmann (check survey), vol. 404, 1955 (Box B16)
  - 3 Mine (levels), vols. 3-15, 1966-1980 (Box B16)
  - Itmann 3 Mine (levels), vols. 20-22, 26-28, 30, 1980-1986 (Box B17)
  - Itmann 3 Mine (survey), vols. 7-9, 92, 1980-1983, 1985 (Box B17)
  - Itmann 3 Mine (CL), vol. 3, 1976-1977 (Box B17)
  - Unidentified, 1963 (Box B17)
  - No. 3 Mine (levels), vols. 12-22, 1975-1981 (Box B17)
  - No. 2 Mine (CL & 1/4 survey), vols. 7, 9-27, 30, 34, 37-38, 1962-1977 (Box B17)
    (31 ledgers)
  - No. 2 Mine (CL & 1/4 survey), vols. 27-30, 34, 37-39, 1977-1986 (Box B18)
  - No. 2 Mine, vols. 28-30, 1977-1980 (Box B18)
  - No. 2 Mine (CL), vols. 3-26, 1959-1975 (Box B18)
    (24 ledgers)
  - No. 2 Mine (levels), vols. 2-9, 14, 1966-1980, 1986 (Box B18)
  - No. 2 Mine (levels), 1967 (Box B18)
  - No. 2 Mine (levels), vols. 2-6, 9, 1967-1977, 1980 (Box B18)
  - No. 2 Mine (check survey), vol. 2, 1969-1975 (Box B18)
  - No. 2 Mine, vols. 5, 8, 1961, 1963-1964 (Box B18)
  - Ritter Property, Book 1-5, 1968-1969 (Box B19)
  - Kepler, vols. 1-5, 1970 (Box B19)
  - Pocahontas House and Lot Location, vols. 7701-A, 7702, 7705, 7707, 7708, 1952-1958 (Box B19)
  - Bland Co. Lands, vols, 2-3, 5, 1950-1971 (Box B19)
  - Cross Sections, 5101-5103, 5110B, VR, 1956 (Box B19)
  - Bland Co., 1955 (Box B19)
  - VR (levels), vol. 6500, 1956 (Box B19)
  - Peerless Lot Loc., 1957 (Box B19)
  - Levels over Robinate and Joe’s Branch, 1968 (Box B19)
  - Survey 2102, 1956 (Box B19)
  - Mine 87, vol. 2101, 1956 (Box B19)
  - Sewell Seam/Ritter, 1964 (Box B19)
  - Pocahontas Water (?), 1953 (Box B19)
  - Greasey Creek, 1977 (Box B19)
  - Unidentified, 1954 (Box B19)
  - Arista, Transit Books, 1914-1920 (Box B19)
  - Arista, vols. 28, 31-33, 42, 1935, 1944 (Box B19)
  - Arista, 1917-1923 (Box B20)
  - Modoc Mine (levels), vols. 1-7, 1971-1979 (Box B20)
  - Rich Creek, 1971 (Box B20)
  - Fossil Fuel Co., 1979-1980 (Box B20)
  - Piedmont, vol. 2, 1976 (Box B20)
  - Noseman Branch, vol. 2, 1980-1981 (Box B20)
  - Modoc Mine, 1972-1978 (Box B20)
  - Turkey Gap, 1972-1980 (Box B20)
  - [Scrap] (Box B20)
  - Assorted survey books (Box B20)
  - Mine nos. 1-3, SPADS, and Matthews Mine No. 3, 1960s-1980s (Box B21)
    (58 ledgers)
  - Amonate #3 (CL), vols. 1-31, 1977-1988 (Box B22)
  - Amonate #3, vol. 1105, 1970-1971 (Box B22)
  - [Itmann] No. 1 Mine (CL), vols. 478-480, 1981-1985 (Box B22)
  - No. 3 Mine (check survey), vols. 5-8, 1974-1983 (Box B22)
  - S&C Mine No. 7 & 8 (CL), vols. 3-5, 1975-1984 (Box B22)
  - S&C Mine No. 7 & 8 (levels), vol. 1, 1974-1983 (Box B22)
  - No. 2 Mine (levels), vols. 11-13, 1981-1985 (Box B22)
  - No. 2 Mine (CL), vols. 34-38, 1982-1986 (Box B22)
  - No. 3 Mine (levels), vols. 26-28, 1982-1985 (Box B22)
  - Itmann No. 3 Mine (CL), vols. 86-91, 95, 1982-1986 (Box B23)
  - Crane Creek No. 9 and 12 Seam, 1981-1982 (Box B23)
  - Eckman-Page (survey books), vols. 1-3, 21-23, 1973-1982 (Box B23)
  - JenkinJones No. 4 Seam (field books), 1976-1981 (Box B23)
  - Modoc Mine, 1970-1978 (Box B23)
    (11 vols.)
  - Turkey Gap, 1972-1981 (Box B23)
  - Crane Creek, 1981 (Box B23)
  - Covel, 1976-1978 (Box B23)
  - Survey notebooks for mine sites, including Arista Mains, Chrysler, 1970s-1980s (Box B23)
  - #1 Mine, 1967-1971 (Box B24)
  - #2 Mine, 1968-1969 (Box B24)
  - #3 Mine, 1969-1971 (Box B24)
  - Inside survey books, 1967-1990 (Box B24)
  - Outside survey books, 1968-1978 (Box B24)
  - Consol Coal Co. (drill hole elevations), 1967-1968 (Box B24)
  - Coal Sections – Mining Heights and Widths, 1976 (Box B24)
  - Prospect openings, 1973 (Box B24)
  - Amonate (check survey), vols. 1-3, 1977-1989 (Box B25)
  - No. 31, 1946-1959 (Box B25)
  - Amo #31 (CL), vols. 13-15, 1982-1983 (Box B25)
  - Amo (1/4 survey), vols. 11-17, 1983-1985 (Box B25)
  - Amonate (CL), vol. 37, 1989 (Box B25)
  - Amonate (CL), vols. 1-14, 17-52, 1977-1994 (Box B25)
    (50 ledgers)
  - Book 2-11, 1962 (Box B26)
  - Unidentified, 1956-1967 (Box B26)
  - Trimore Mine, 1956-1968 (Box B26)
    (33 vols.)
  - Redbird (levels), 1970 (Box B26)
  - Vol. 19, 1966 (Box B26)
  - Old Moore Mine, 1954 (Box B26)
  - Various mines, Vols. 351-375, 1950-1953 (Box B27)
    (25 ledgers)
  - Itmann, vols. 352-375, 1950-1953 (Box B27)
  - Turkey Gap, 1981 (Box B27)
  - Turkey Gap, 1979, 1981-1983 (Box B28)
  - No. 1 Mine, vols. 476-481, 1980-1986 (Box B28)
  - No. 2 Mine (CL), vols. 33, 35, 36, 39, 1981-1986 (Box B28)
  - No. 2 Mine (levels), vols. 12-13, 1982-1985 (Box B28)
  - No. 2 Mine (check survey), vol. 3, 1978-1981 (Box B28)
  - No. 2 Mine (survey), vol. 4, 1982 (Box B28)
  - Guyandotte (1/4 survey), vol. 2, 1959 (Box B28)
  - Deerfield, vols. 1-12, 1956-1960 (Box B28)
  - No. 1 Mine (levels), vols. 2-4, 1966-1970 (Box B28)
  - No. 1 Mine, 1960-1963, 1970-1975 (Box B28)
  - Assorted survey books (Box B28)
  - Morco Mine, 1967-1969 (Box B29)
  - Sagamore, 1945-1967 (Box B29)
  - Jenkin Jones, 1968-1981 (Box B29)
    (22 vols.)
  - Cherokee, 1931-1953 (Box B29)
  - Turkey Gap, 1963 (Box B29)
  - Piedmont, 1969-1970 (Box B29)
  - Greenbrier, 1975 (Box B29)
  - No. 1 Mine, 1962, 1967-1969 (Box B30)
  - No. 3 Mine, vols. 81-82, 1980-1981 (Box B30)
  - Deerfield, vol. 21, 1960 (Box B30)
  - Deerfield side, vol. 668 (Box B30)
  - Guyandotte, vols. 1, 5, 1960 (Box B30)
  - No. 3 Mine (levels), vol.1, 1960 (Box B30)
  - No. 3 Mine (check survey), 1967 (Box B30)
  - No.3 Mine (survey), vols. 3-5, 1971-1975 (Box B30)
  - No. 3 Mine (CL), vols. 6-29, 48, 59, 1961-1974 (Box B30)
    (26 ledgers)
  - L&M #2 (CL), vol. 1, 1980 (Box B30)
  - Buckeye Mine (CL), vols. 21-23, 1974-1976 (Box B30)
  - Buckeye Mine, vol. 4, 1964 (Box B30)
  - Buckeye (levels), 1966-1970 (Box B30)
  - Copperhead Br., 1971 (Box B30)
  - Noseman Br., vol. 4, 1967 (Box B30)
  - Buckeye, 6 vols., 1973-1982 (Box B31)
  - Buckeye outside, vol. 100-102, 1973-1979 (Box B31)
  - Buckeye (Stephenson), 3 vols., 1965, 1974-1976 (Box B31)
  - No. 1 Mine (levels), vol. 5, 1971-1977 (Box B31)
  - No. 2 Mine (check survey), vols. 2-3, 1968-1981 (Box B31)
  - No. 3 Mine (check survey), vols. 2-4, 1960-1974 (Box B31)
  - Town of Pageston & Elkhorn, 1970 (Box B31)
  - Dryfork Outside, 1976-1978 (Box B31)
  - Sugar Run, no.1, 1979 (Box B31)
  - Pond Locations, 1981 (Box B31)
  - Eckman, vol.1 (Box B31)
  - G.S.C. #1, 1958-1959 (Box B31)
  - Faraday, H-2117, 1940 (Box B31)
  - Rowland Lands (Box B31)
  - Bishop, 1971-1975 (Box B31)
  - No. 1 Mine (CL) vols. 476-477, 1980-1981 (Box B31)
  - No. 2 Mine (levels), vol. 10, 1980-1981 (Box B31)
  - No. 2 Mine (CL), vols. 31-33, 1980-1982 (Box B31)
  - No. 3 Mine (levels), vols. 23-25, 1981-1982 (Box B31)
  - No. 3 Mine (CL), vols. 83-85, 88-90, 1981-1984 (Box B31)
  - G&A (CL), vol. 1, 1976 (Box B31)
  - Sioux Coal Co. (levels), vol.1, 1976-1979 (Box B31)
  - Bentley & 3C (CL), vol. 2, 1971-1975 (Box B31)
  - Small Transit GT-60 (no. 32), Sokkisha Co. Ltd. pamphlet (Box B31)
  - Assorted survey books, 1957-1965 (Box B31)
  - Extractors (levels), vols. 1-2, 1975-1979 (Box B32)
  - Extractors (CL), vols. 3-4, 1976-1979 (Box B32)
  - Underground Energy (levels), vols. 1-2, 1976-1979 (Box B32)
  - Sioux Coal Co. (CL), vols. 1-3, 1976-1980 (Box B32)
  - Underground Energy (CL), vols. 100-102, 1976-1980 (Box B32)
  - Itmann Outside, 1962-1963 (Box B32)
  - Beckley Auger, 1973 (Box B32)
  - Cabin Creek, C-4501, 1961 (Box B32)
  - Extractors Deep Mine, vols. 1-2, 1975-1976 (Box B32)
  - B&L, 1969-1973 (Box B32)
  - Perry & Hylton, 1968-1970 (Box B32)
  - S&C, 1970-1976 (Box B32)
  - 3C Coal, 1971-1976 (Box B32)
  - Sioux Coal Co., 1976-1980 (Box B32)
  - Underground Energy Levels, 1976-1980 (Box B32)
  - V&R, 1976-1980 (Box B32)
  - Itmann-Beckley, S&C Mine, 1968-1975 (Box B32)
  - G&A (CL), 1977-1982 (Box B32)
  - Sugar Run, vol. 2, 1977-1982 (Box B32)
  - Underground Energy, 1976-1978 (Box B32)
  - Extractors Inc., 1975-1976 (Box B32)
  - Bentley – 3C, 1977-1982 (Box B32)
  - Seven assorted volumes (Box B32)
  - Deerfield (1/4 survey), vols. 641-660, 1956-1959 (Box B33)
  - Itmann (1/4 survey), vols. 641-660, 1956-1959 (Box B33)
  - Whitesville A and S Coal Co., Itmann, Sewell Seam Strip, 1970-1972 (Box B33)
  - Itmann, V-2008, 1975 (Box B33)
  - Odd Jobs, 1979 (Box B33)
  - Two vols., Unidentified, 1979 (Box B33)
  - #4 Seam (Windlebrook Coal Co. Inc.), Vol. 1, 1962 (Box B33)
  - Sewell Seam, Deerfield, Vol. 1, 1963 (Box B33)
  - Red Rose (CL & levels), 1976-1982 (Box B34)
  - Bentley – 3C, 1976 (Box B34)
  - Extractors, 1979-1983 (Box B34)
  - Copperhead, 1967-1971 (Box B34)
  - Beckley Seam, vols. 1-2, 1973-1975 (Box B34)
  - Beckley Seam, vol. 1, 1967 (Box B34)
  - Beckley Seam – Auger Mining, 1973 (Box B34)
  - G&A Coal, 1976-1983 (Box B34)
  - V&R, vols. 1-3, 1976-1980 (Box B34)
  - Odd Jobs, vol. 8, 1983 (Box B34)
  - No. 4 Mine (check survey), vol. 1, 1970 (Box B34)
  - Buckeye Outside, vol. 1-A, 1965 (Box B34)
  - Sugar Run, vol. 1, 1975-1977 (Box B34)
  - Itmann, 1947-1980 (Box B34)
  - Buckeye (levels), vols. 1-7, 1965-1977 (Box B34)
  - Buckeye, vols. 1-17, 1962-1972 (Box B34)
  - Buckeye, vols. 10, 18-24, 1967-1978 (Box B35)
  - Buckeye (check survey), 1974 (Box B35)
  - No. 6 Seam, 1963-1964 (Box B35)
  - Maps, 1965-1973 (Box B35)
  - Arista Mine, 1950-1953 (Box B35)
    (25 vols.)
  - Amonate Outside, vols. 12-13, 707, 710, 1981, 1986 (Box B35)
  - Amonate, 1976-1981 (Box B35)
  - Crane Creek, 1957-1983 (Box B36)
    (65 vols.)
  - Crane Creek, 1957-1983 (Box B37)
    (29 vols.)
  - Unidentified, 1973-1981 (Box B37)
  - JenkinJones, 1974-1976 (Box B37)
  - Levels 8-1, Genoa Punch, Vol. 1, 1970 (Box B37)
  - Vol. L, 11-A, 1966 (Box B37)
  - Itmann and Deerfield, 1956-1958 (Box B37)
  - Amonate (CL), vols. 32-49, 1988-1993 (Box B38)
    (18 ledgers)
  - Amonate (levels), vols. 1-5, 7-17, 19, 1978-1989 (Box B38)
  - Amonate (levels), vols. 1-6, 1990 (Box B38)
  - Amonate (B-right), 1991 (Box B38)
  - Amonate (levels on RR), vols. 7-22, 1990 (Box B38)
    (16 ledgers)
  - Volume, 1992 (Box B38)
  - Amonate (levels), vols. 1-21, 1978-1989 (Box B39)
    (21 ledgers)
  - Itmann, 1947-1955 (Box B39)
  - Five assorted volumes, 1960-1963 (Box B39)
  - Wyoming Mining Corp., 1939-1955 (Box B39)
  - Crozer Coal, 1946-1949 (Box B39)
  - Itmann Levels, 1950-1960 (Box B40)
    (34 vols.)
  - Assorted levels, 1950-1960 (Box B40)
  - Crozer Coal, 1947-1955 (Box B41)
  - No. 3 Mine, vols. 30-47, 1965-1971 (Box B41)
  - No. 3 Mine (CL), vols. 50-58, 60-64, 66-69, 71-72, 1972-1977 (Box B41)
  - No. 3 Mine (CL & 1/4 survey), vols. 8-16, 1961-1963 (Box B41)
  - Assorted levels, vols. 521-534, 1955-1958 (Box B42)
  - Pocahontas, 1942-1954 (Box B42)
  - Beech fork, 1972-1976 (Box B42)
  - Land lines, undated (Box B42)
  - Faraday, 1927-1943 (Box B42)
  - Amonate, 1955-1956 (Box B42)
  - Bishop, 1934-1973 (Box B42)
  - Boissevain, undated (Box B42)
  - Vols. 9011-9035, 1945-1956 (Box B42)
  - Dunford Portal, 1955 (Box B42)
  - Elmira Coal Co., 1979 (Box B42)
  - No. 3 Mine (CL & 1/4 survey), vols. 17-63, 1963-1975 (Box B43)
    (47 ledgers)
  - No. 3 Mine (CL), vols. 64-82, 1975-1981 (Box B44)
  - Itmann (CL), vols. 377-395, 1953-1954 (Box B44)
  - Itmann (CL), vols. 376-388, 390-391, 1953-1954 (Box B44)
  - Itmann (CL), vols. 392-395, 1954-1955 (Box B45)
  - Amonate (check survey), vols. 1-4, 1977-1989 (Box B45)
  - Amonate (levels), vols. 5-6, 1980-1981 (Box B45)
  - Amonate (levels), vols. 18, 20-22, 1988-1994 (Box B45)
  - Amonate (CL), vols. 50-52, 1993-1994 (Box B45)
  - Amonate (1/4 survey), 1979-1985 (Box B45)
  - Amonate, 1978-1988 (Box B45)
  - S&C (CL), vols. 1-2, 1972-1979 (Box B45)
  - Center District, vol. 3, 1981 (Box B45)
  - Sugar Run (CL), vols. 1-2, 1975-1979 (Box B45)
  - Red Rose Coal Co., Westigan Inc., 1976-1983 (Box B45)
  - Berwind, 1962-1964 (Box B46)
  - Bishop Outside, 1931-1970 (Box B46)
  - Beech Fork, 1974-1977 (Box B46)
  - Vols. 9036, 9038A, 9039A, 9039-9043, 1953-1956 (Box B46)
  - Faraday, 1930-1942 (Box B46)
  - Pocahontas Corp., 1942 (Box B46)
  - Pigeon Branch, 1969-1974 (Box B46)
  - Assorted volumes, 1935-1974 (Box B46)
  - No. 2 Mine, levels, vols. 7-8, 10-11, 31-32 (Box B47)
  - No. 3 Mine, survey, CL, and levels, vols. 6, 16-19, 23-25, 83-84 (Box B47)
  - Extractors (levels and CL), vols. 1-5 (Box B47)
  - 3-C Coal Co. and Bentley, vols. 1, 2, 4, and 5, 1970-1982 (Box B47)
  - G and A Coal Co. No. 2 (CL), vols. 1-3 (Box B47)
  - G and A Coal Co. (levels), vols. 1-2 (Box B47)
  - G and A Coal Co. (survey), vol. 1, 1977-1982 (Box B47)
  - Freestone/Hiope (CL & levels), vols. 1-8, 1982-1989 (Box B47)
  - G and A Coal Co. (CL & levels), vols. 1-13, 1986-1993 (Box B47)
  - McGlothlin (CL & levels), vols. 2-7, 1991-1994 (Box B47)
  - Itmann, ca. 1950s-1980s (Box B48)
  - Guyandotte, ca. 1950s-1980s (Box B48)
  - Cabin Creek, ca. 1950s-1980s (Box B48)
  - Beckley, ca. 1950s-1980s (Box B48)
  - Deerfield, ca. 1950s-1980s (Box B48)
  - Bishop, ca. 1950s-1980s (Box B48)
  - Lynco Mines, ca. 1950s-1980s (Box B48)
  - Crane Creek, ca. 1950s-1980s (Box B48)
  - Pocahontas, ca. 1950s-1980s (Box B48)
  - Hiope No. 6, vols. 1-2, 1995 (Box B49)
  - Hiope No. 4, vols. 2,4, 1992-1994 (Box B49)
  - Clinch Valley No. 5, vols. 3-4, 1994-1995 (Box B49)
  - Gordie Coal, vol. 3, 1994 (Box B49)
  - Greasy Creek No. 2 (CL and levels), vols. 1-8, 1989-1994 (Box B49)
  - Greasy Creek, vols. 9-10, 1989-1994 (Box B49)
  - Greasy Creek Coal Company (CL and levels), vols. 3-6, 1986-1989 (Box B49)
  - Amonate Outside, vols. 711-713, 715, 717-718, 720-721, 1985-1993 (Box B49)
  - Bear Ridge (CL and levels), vols. 3-10, 1987-1993 (Box B49)
  - Fiddle Coal Co. (CL and levels), vols. 4-10, 1987-1992 (Box B49)